{"data":[{"question":"Gunpowder, in some ways the most effective of all the explosive materials, ________ a mixture of potassium nitrate, charcoal, and sulfur.","a":"were","b":"had been","c":"had","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- When the sentence is separated by a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence , words lie between these two commas are not essential to the meaning of the sentence and they don't affect sentence structure.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"In the relatively short history of industrial ________ in the United States, New York city has played a vital role.","a":"developed","b":"development","c":"developing","d":"develop","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Of + Verb-ing\/noun\/noun phrase\/pronoun.\u00a0\n- Noun phrase: Adj + Noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"As the demand increases, manufacturers who previously produced only a large, luxury car ________ compelled to make a smaller model in order to compete in the market.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"will","d":"should","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Subject (manufacturers) is plural.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She has ________ the conditions for entry into the college.","a":"satisfied","b":"satisfaction","c":"satisfactory","d":"satisfactorily","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: have\/has+ PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"For the first time in the history of the country, the person ________ was recommended by the president to replace a retiring justice on the supreme court is a woman.","a":"which","b":"whose","c":"who","d":"whom","answer":"3","explain":"\u00a0\n- We use who (pronoun) as the subject in the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Signor Risponso's fame rested on the breadth of his range, which was ________ any other tenor, living or dead.","a":"greater than that of","b":"as large as","c":"more greater","d":"broader than the one of","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the comparative form of short adjective (great)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"New words are constantly being invented ________ new objects and concepts.","a":"to describe","b":"a description of","c":"they describe","d":"describe","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To invent + to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You can't ________ to learn a foreign language in a week.","a":"expectant","b":"expected","c":"expect","d":"expectation","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Can\/can't + Infinitive (without to).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"________ rain or snow there are always more than fifty thousand fans at the football games.","a":"Despite","b":"In spite with","c":"Despite of","d":"Despite with","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Despite + Noun\/noun phrase.\u00a0\n- In spite of + Noun\/noun phrase.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The prices of homes are ________ high in urban areas that most young people cannot afford to buy them.","a":"as","b":"so","c":"such","d":"so as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- So\/such...that: used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is.\u00a0\n+ So + adj + that.\u00a0\n+ Such + noun phrase ((a)adj + noun).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}